export const quiz ={
  topic: 'javascript',
  level: 'beginner',
  totalQuestions: 25,
  perQuestionScore: 1,

  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who is the Father of Abraham?',
      choices: ['Isaac', 'Noah', 'Terah', 'none of the above'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Terah',
    },
    {
      question: 'And Moses Married_____ the Daughter of ______',
      choices: ['Mariam, Pharaoh', 'Zipporah, Jabez', 'Deborah, Jethro', 'Zipporah, Jethro'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Zipporah, Jethro',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the priest when David ate the hallowed bread?',
      choices: ['Eleazar', 'Ahimelech', 'Ithamar', 'Zechariah'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Ahimelech',
    },
    {
      question: 'Jonathan is whose son?',
      choices: ['Saul', 'David', 'Samuel', 'Eli'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Saul',
    },
    {
      question: 'Aceldama means what?',
      choices: ['It is finished', 'Field of blood', 'Arise', 'Be opened'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Field of blood',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who betrayed Jesus?',
      choices: ['Jabez', 'John', 'Jacob', 'None of the above'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'None of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ephphatha means?',
      choices: ['Be opened', 'My lord My lord why hath thou forsaken me?', 'Be stilled', 'None of the above'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Be opened',
    },
    {
      question: 'Seth begat ______',
      choices: ['Enoch', 'Lamech', 'Enos', 'Elijah'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Enos',
    },
    {
      question: 'Cain means?',
      choices: ['Replace', 'Gotten', 'Stone', 'Gold'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Gotten',
    },
    {
      question: 'In the year that king Uzziah died',
      choices: ['I died', 'I came alive', 'I saw the Lord', 'I rose up'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'I saw the Lord',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who denied Jesus?',
      choices: ['Jabez', 'John', 'Jacob', 'Peter'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Peter',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the oldest man in the bible',
      choices: ['Methuselah', 'Lamech', 'Jared', 'Mahalaleel'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Methuselah',
    },
    {
      question: 'The oldest man of the bible died at the age of?',
      choices: ['696years', '639years', '980years', '969years'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '969years',
    },
    {
      question: 'The longest verse of the whole bible is?',
      choices: ['James 3:10', 'Esther 6:9', 'Genesis 2:20', 'John 11:35'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Esther 6:9',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why persecuted thou me? was said to who?',
      choices: ['Festus', 'Herod', 'Peter', 'Saul'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Saul',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who replaced Judas?',
      choices: ['Barsabas', 'Matthias', 'Joseph', 'Justus'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Matthias',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the uncle of Esther?',
      choices: ['Mordecai', 'Herod', 'Simon', 'Matthew'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Mordecai',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the longest chapter of the bible?',
      choices: ['Revelation 22', 'Genesis 50', 'Psalm 118', 'Psalm 119'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Psalm 119',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the mother of John the baptist?',
      choices: ['Rebecca', 'Esther', 'Elizabeth', 'Salome'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Elizabeth',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the first person to see Peter when he came out of the prison?',
      choices: ['Rhoda', 'Mary', 'Eunice', 'Loiz'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Rhoda',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the priest that took over after Aaron?',
      choices: ['Abihu', 'Nadab', 'Ithamar', 'Eleazar'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Eleazar',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the successor of Moses?',
      choices: ['Levi', 'Joshua', 'Amram', 'Caleb'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Joshua',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many human entered the Ark made by Noah?',
      choices: ['8', '12', '7', '18'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '8',
    },
    {
      question: 'David is number what son of Jesse?',
      choices: ['3', '6', '7', '8'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '8',
    },
    {
      question: 'This i say then, Walk in the Spirit, and ye shall not fulfil the lust of the flesh. Can be found where?',
      choices: ['Ephesians 6:10', 'Galatians 5:16', 'Galatians 3:6', '1Corinthians 3:16'],
      types: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Galatians 5:16',
    }
    
  ],
}